[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song by The Beatles, recorded during the Sgt. Pepper sessions, contains the lyrics: \nBehind the shelter in the middle of a roundabout \nThe pretty nurse is selling poppies from a tray?", "correct_answer": "Penny Lane", "incorrect_answers": ["Help!", "Strawberry Fields Forever", "A Hard Days Night"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is how much the risk of breast cancer increases, if a woman eats meat daily, as opposed to once a week only.", "correct_answer": "3.8 times", "incorrect_answers": ["2.8 times", "2 times", "3 times"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of his visual acting style, Rowan Atkinson is often compared to this legendary actor.", "correct_answer": "Charlie Chaplin", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert De Niro", "Benny Hill", "Jim Carrey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor delivered the following movie line: I reckon Im looking at a tin star with a drunk pinned on it!?", "correct_answer": "John Wayne to Robert Mitchum", "incorrect_answers": ["Clint Eastwood to Eli Wallach", "John Wayne to Eli Wallach", "Will Geer to John Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hey, you stay away from the frozen foods section. Your boobsll harden is a bit of dialog from which movie?", "correct_answer": "Big Daddy", "incorrect_answers": ["Super Troopers", "Half Baked", "How High"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "IRC lets people all over the world chat in virtual rooms, called channels.", "correct_answer": "Internet Relay Chat", "incorrect_answers": ["Internet Rough Chat", "Internet Reality Chat", "Internet Real Chat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Indonesian island is shared by four Indonesian provinces and two other nations: the eastern half of Malaysia and the tiny oil-rich sultanate of Brunei?", "correct_answer": "Borneo", "incorrect_answers": ["New Guinea", "Sumatra", "Flores"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular movie director initially negotiated the offer to direct the 2001 movie Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone, but eventually turned it down?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["George Lucas", "Robert Zemeckis", "Luc Besson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the vengeful murderer in the 1992 thriller movie The Hand That Rocks the Cradle?", "correct_answer": "The nanny", "incorrect_answers": ["The gardener", "Dr. Victor Mott", "The real estate agent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these shades of purple can be found in a box of Crayola Crayons?", "correct_answer": "All of the Above", "incorrect_answers": ["Vivid Violet", "Royal Purple", "Purple Mountains Majesty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This shark was believed to be extinct, until it was found on the coast of Japan in 1898.", "correct_answer": "goblin shark", "incorrect_answers": ["cookie cutter shark", "mako shark", "angel shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These substances act as moisturisers by attracting water to themselves, even from the air.  They are also used to prevent creams from drying out.", "correct_answer": "Humectants", "incorrect_answers": ["Surfactants", "Preservatives", "Antioxidants"]}]